const Questions = [
    {
      "question": "I have cities, but no houses; forests, but no trees; and water, but no fish. What am I?",
      "optionA": "A. Map",
      "optionB": "B. Painting",
      "optionC": "C. Dream",
      "optionD": "D. Reflection",
      "answer": "A. Map"
    },
    {
      "question": "I have keys, but no locks; space, but no room; you can enter, but can't go inside. What am I?",
      "optionA": "A. Book",
      "optionB": "B. Website",
      "optionC": "C. Keyboard",
      "optionD": "D. Puzzle box",
      "answer": "C. Keyboard"
    },
    {
      "question": "I have a neck, but no head; a body, but no legs; and I wear a coat, but never feel cold. What am I?",
      "optionA": "A. Tree trunk",
      "optionB": "B. Guitar",
      "optionC": "C. Statue",
      "optionD": "D. Bottle",
      "answer": "D. Bottle"
    },
    {
      "question": "I am always coming, but never arrive; always present, but never here. What am I?",
      "optionA": "A. Silence",
      "optionB": "B. Tomorrow",
      "optionC": "C. Your reflection",
      "optionD": "D. The horizon",
      "answer": "B. Tomorrow"
    },
    {
      "question": "I can be cracked, but not broken; held, but not touched; and spoken, but not heard. What am I?",
      "optionA": "A. Promise",
      "optionB": "B. Secret",
      "optionC": "C. Code",
      "optionD": "D. Joke",
      "answer": "C. Code"
    },
    {
      "question": "I have pages, but no words; a spine, but no bones; and I can tell you a story, but have no voice. What am I?",
      "optionA": "A. Book",
      "optionB": "B. Calendar",
      "optionC": "C. Map",
      "optionD": "D. Diary",
      "answer": "A. Book"
    },
    {
      "question": "I am lighter than air, but can crush the mightiest tree. I have no voice, but can roar like a beast. What am I?",
      "optionA": "A. Wind",
      "optionB": "B. Time",
      "optionC": "C. Silence",
      "optionD": "D. Thought",
      "answer": "A. Wind"
    },
    {
      "question": "I travel the world, but never leave my corner. I see everything, but have no eyes. What am I?",
      "optionA": "A. Mirror",
      "optionB": "B. Stamp",
      "optionC": "C. Window",
      "optionD": "D. Map",
      "answer": "B. Stamp"
    },
    {
        "question": "I have a heart that doesn't beat. I can flow without water. What am I?",
        "optionA": "A. River",
        "optionB": "B. Clock",
        "optionC": "C. Tree",
        "optionD": "D. Road",
        "answer": "B. Clock"
    },
    {
        "question": "Extracted from mines, enclosed in wood, never freed, yet widely used. What am I?",
        "optionA": "A. Gold",
        "optionB": "B. Diamond",
        "optionC": "C. Coal",
        "optionD": "D. Pencil Lead",
        "answer": "D. Pencil Lead"
    }
];

export default Questions;
